<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yakin Rubaiat</title>
    <link>https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yakin Rubaiat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Report On Pima Indian Diabetes Dataset</title>
      <link>https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/report-on-pima-indian-diabetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/report-on-pima-indian-diabetes/</guid>
      <description>1. Abstract In this study, we have proposed an analysis of different method based on a neural network for predicting type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM). The main problems that we are trying to solve are to find which type of model works best for predicting diabetes. The analysis is comprised of two parts, by applying data-recovery with the neural network and by applying k-means with the neural network. The consultation shows that why some model is good at predicting diabetes and is it computationally expensive or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A small project example : add yours !</title>
      <link>https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/small-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yakinrubaiat.github.io/projects/small-project/</guid>
      <description>Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.
 He rather enjoys tea, but seems to have trouble obtaining it in the far reaches of the galaxy.
 In time, he learns how to fly and carves a niche for himself as a sandwich-maker.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>